(Previously)
I already see a card.
Let's see what it is.
PROJECT XY
will soon welcome the seventh member.
He will have a special privilege.
Get ready
to welcome the new member.
Is the newbie here?
Over there.
(Epiosde 4: Newcomers
Undercurrents)
HELLO, everyone.
I'm Alan.
I studied dance performance.
After graduation,
I joined an airline
and became a flight attendant.
The main reason I joined this show.
The biggest reason is
I want to challenge myself
with the profession of acting.
And the ideal partner in my mind,
his image is someone
thoughtful,
gentle and considerate,
good at putting himself in others' shoes,
and empathetic.
Although I'm the last to arrive,
I believe
I can blend in quickly.
I hope to find
a partner I like here.
Oh, it's him.
Hello.
Everyone is so handsome.
Welcome.
Hello.
Hi.
Everyone is so handsome.
Let's move over here.
You sit here.
OK.
Then we'll sit here.
He looks like he's from Xinjiang.
Are you from Xinjiang?
No.
I'm from Hunan.
Hunan? I'm also from Hunan.
Are you from Hunan?
I'm from Hengyang, Hunan.
Where are you from?
I am from Zhuzhou.
Zhuzhou, that's very close.
Do you have a nickname?
Alan, I guess.
Cheche.
Yes.
Just call me Joel.
Joel.
You can call me Waner.
Waner.
Yes.
And my name is Young.
You can call me Xiaoxu.
Or Yangyang, either is fine.
Elio.
Tyler.
CH.
OK, let me test you.
Test you.
It's okay, take your time.
You'll remember after
spending more time together.
We couldn't remember
at the beginning either.
So you're a singer?
No.
Not a singer.
As for me,
the industries I've
worked in are quite varied.
Quite varied.
Yes, that's right.
I've done,
I worked as a flight attendant for 8 years.
Later I went into the
live streaming industry.
So versatile.
Can do all kinds of things.
And all in front of the camera,
on-camera work.
Yeah, quite rich in experience.
Before you came,
we were guessing your zodiac sign.
I'm Libra.
Libra.
We're air signs.
Air signs, we've added another one.
Which month's Libra?
I'm October.
I'm September.
I'm September 27th.
Because our current group is
two air signs,
two fire signs and two water signs.
So we were guessing
whether the seventh member
would be an earth sign.
OK.
Then I think you're an I personality.
I tested as an E.
E.
ENTJ.
E what?
Completely different.
We're all N.
You're the first one here,
the first T personality.
T people are
rational personality.
Rational.
F is emotional.
T is rational.
We have three INFJs here.
Not a single T person?
No, all F.
Alright.
On this card just now, it said
you have a privilege.
So what is the privilege?
I didn't even notice.
This.
He will have a special privilege.
So you guys yesterday
shot those CP photos, right?
Yes.
And today my privilege is
I can choose one more person
to shoot another CP photo session with me.
So any one of us?
Yes, that's right.
Then who do you want to pick?
Choose.
Is there anyone
who wants to,
is there anyone who wants to shoot with me?
Don't you choose yourself?
Any one of us are fine.
It's your privilege.
Yes, it's your privilege, you choose.
OK, sure.
Then you're closer to me.
I'll choose you then.
OK, no problem.
Congratulations.
No problem.
Choosing Young for this CP photo,
it's because his skin is very fair.
I just think he's quite handsome.
Maybe because I'm closer to him.
That's what I think.
Then let's start now.
So we can design the
poses on the spot, right?
Sure, OK.
Any ideas?
Let me think.
If we shoot here, is there.
Are we shooting directly here?
Shouldn't we go to the beach?
Shoot on the beach, right?
But yesterday every
group was very intimate.
So your group can't not be intimate.
Must be intimate.
Has to be more intimate
than we were yesterday.
Is it punishment for coming late?
Why isn't it a reward?
Looking forward to your photos.
Can we go watch, or?
Sure, let's start then.
Looking forward to your photos.
Everyone staring at me while shooting,
I feel embarrassed.
Yesterday the two of us
he no one staring.
I still felt embarrassed.
Come on.
Let's go.
Are there that many poses?
Actually not that many.
But
let me try to think of as many as I can.
How about we shoot over here?
Then we'll move closer to the sea later.
Because I'm afraid
the sand over there might be a bit dirty.
Would you... do you want to lie down?
I'm afraid you might think it's too dirty.
I'm fine with it.
You're going to lie down?
Then be careful.
It's a bit hot.
Let's go over there.
That side is cleaner.
No, the background is cleaner there.
Let's go.
Let's do it here then.
Let's not go any further.
OK, sure.
If we go further, there'll be a railing.
You lie down at a spot,
then I need to hold myself up.
And then basically kneel
or sit.
OK, I'll sit first.
Like this?
How were you yesterday?
We were the kind
who just love to watch the fun.
That kind, we were
bystanders.
We're art directors.
Come on, body movement director on duty.
You shot with him yesterday,
you can help guide him.
Yesterday we could sink into the sand.
I can't sink into this.
Tyler, come over here.
Are they in the same color scheme?
They really match.
Quite compatible, both
their clothes really match.
Pants match too.
I think they can try this pose.
Just lean like this,
and then just fall back.
Want me to pull them?
Sure, you can go.
Really, you can go.
No.
Switch to a different pose.
You lean back a bit,
then tilt your head back.
Yes, just like that.
Let me think, how to make it look better?
Actually I was thinking we could sit.
Let's demonstrate it for him.
What we were talking about.
Yeah, you go.
We're art directors.
Can we give some advice?
Wait.
Quick, help guide us, bros.
We were talking about
then you lie down too.
I'll lie down.
(ART DIRECTOR ONLINE)
Come on, you lie down first.
You lie down and I'll find my position.
I should... we were thinking like this.
And you should be lying over here.
Yes, and then like this.
Then lie down.
Then the two of us...
No, it's like this.
What I was thinking is
both looking at the sky.
Yes.
Wait, you lie on me.
You lie in my arms.
In my arms.
Come on, this definitely works.
I lie down, right?
OK, come on.
You can kneel, and I'll lie in your arms.
I lie in your...
Like this.
OK.
This works too.
Let's try his idea first, okay?
OK.
Then I'll lie down with confidence.
Lie down with confidence.
So shy.
Quite compatible.
100 points.
OK?
Holding this pose makes me so embarrassed.
Your noses can get closer.
You can get closer.
(HERE FOR THE DRAMA)
You weren't this shy yesterday.
Yeah, yesterday wasn't like this.
We'll do it.
(A CHORUS OF "WOW")
Young is already fidgeting.
I've already squeezed sand in my hands.
Shipping.
You guys made me nervous.
There will still be a bit
of embarrassment.
Because after all, it's our first meeting.
A person as expressive as Young
got shy.
I'm already shy.
I've given it my all.
I still had some,
but now I can't think of anything.
My mind went blank.
You still have one more pose.
You still have one more, you have to do it.
There's more?
You need to take three photos.
Still missing one, right?
Yes.
Let me think.
Then let me think of a standing one.
Standing, just a bit intimate is fine.
(INTRUDING WITH A BAD IDEA)
I have a mischievous idea brewing.
OK, bro, come on.
OK?
I'm fine.
A bit too ordinary.
Too ordinary.
Then how about this?
No, still too ordinary.
Ordinary makes it more down-to-earth.
Otherwise if every one is so stunning,
I'm afraid you can't handle it.
I have one that can make you
open your eyes wide.
Really?
You have one that can
make me open my eyes wide?
Come on.
You'd better not only half-listen.
Blow sand.
Blow sand?
He's going to guide you.
Like this?
You guys are enough.
Not enough, seems like one more.
Come on.
Hurry.
Come on, Young lie down.
I lie down?
It's me lying down again.
Why is it always me lying down?
Just do it.
Good work.
Then how should I be?
What was I thinking of doing?
I find it funny.
Come on, open your legs a bit.
What?
Open flat.
How do you open flat?
Splits.
(ACTION DIRECTOR TAKES OVER)
Lie down.
Don't kneel on me.
Wait.
I guarantee this pose will
make you open your eyes wide.
Sorry.
That's too weird.
Oh my god.
(THE SPECTATORS ARE THRILLED)
The pose has no aesthetic.
You know?
You can lie down more gracefully.
You can lie down,
and then I'll
kneel, is that okay?
I wanted to complete one that I didn't
didn't finish in the last pose.
I want to try again.
Lie down.
Sorry for the trouble.
Lie down, lie down with confidence.
Lie on my knees.
OK.
And then like this, I look at you.
Young's CEO persona is on.
CEO persona coming on.
CEO persona on.
CEO persona is on.
Yes.
I think he is a very enthusiastic
and also very kind person.
We did quickly.
Because he chose me to shoot,
and we worked together.
Just collaborating.
We took great photos together.
OK?
OK.
Great.
Dream fulfilled?
This CEO role today
was good.
CEO dream fulfilled.
Thanks.
Coordination, our
coordination is super high.
Great.
Let's go.
Shot again.
Dream fulfilled.
Fulfilled the dream with this one.
Satisfied.
I'll sit here.
Played the CEO,
took the photos.
Very beautiful.
Any thoughts?
Interviewing you two.
It feels okay.
Not as awkward as I imagined.
No? Then I've already
I'm already shy.
You're shy?
Then maybe I'm still a bit
the type that gets shy easily.
Were you shy yesterday or today?
Your question is so sharp.
What should I do? How should I answer?
Yesterday, today was more shy.
I think it's a different kind of shyness.
Like first love and true love.
Who is the first love?
It must be the first one you meet.
Right?
And then when we meet again,
the feeling is definitely
a different kind of shyness, right?
Different kind of shyness.
Yes.
Shipping them.
Shipping.
Will you be sad?
Me?
It's okay, he's still sharing
a room with me tonight.
Wait, don't.
I feel the atmosphere is a bit
making me nervous.
Yeah, later tonight
when Young goes back to the room,
he'll find the door locked from inside.
What if there's a
room-swapping challenge tonight?
Guess who
shares a room with whom.
Are you two in one room?
We're not.
No.
Then.
Rooms were randomly assigned.
Yes.
You two?
And you two?
Yes, because that day we drew strings.
We pulled strings.
Pulled strings and the two who got
the same string
shared a room.
Isn't there another piece?
The words here are different from before.
Today's XY Drop House is now open.
We've prepared various
surprise ingredients for everyone.
Please work together to complete
all of today's XY Drop House challenges.
To get more food for
tonight's romantic beach party,
acquire more delicious food.
So we need to
get ingredients through tasks.
Yes, just like
the first day.
Like the ping pong game to get ingredients.
Fight for ingredients.
What ingredient do you
want the most right now?
Is it beef?
Beef.
Beef warrior.
I feel like we're at the beach,
how come there's no seafood?
Sea cow.
So where do we find it?
No, isn't there a table over there?
Is it over there?
Over there.
There's also a rule board there.
Let's go.
So smart, bro.
I was thinking of splitting into teams.
Mission board.
What is this?
XY Timed Relay Race.
Rule: within 1 minute 30 seconds,
complete all relay segments.
Can practice multiple times
until completion.
One: Chest Pop Balloon Challenge.
Two people face each
other, holding a balloon
without using hands,
walk the designated path
and pop it at the finish line.
Complete three times to succeed.
That one.
Two: Cookie Stick Challenge.
Rule: two people bite opposite
ends of a thin cookie stick.
It can't break or fall.
The closer you bite,
less than 1cm apart is victory.
1cm.
Everyone knows this one.
Just eating the cookie face to face.
Three: Fruit Kiss Challenge.
Rule: two people hold a fruit between them,
moving it from forehead to waist.
During this time, the fruit cannot leave
either person's body.
Delivering one fruit counts as a success.
Four: Cuddle Roll.
That mat.
Rule: two people hold each other
without letting go,
roll continuously from start to finish.
Success if they don't break apart.
Just rolling.
Roll while holding each other.
Just rolling there.
OK.
Yes.
For each challenge completed,
the group gets one XY voucher.
Got it.
Four games.
Then we definitely have
someone
someone will play twice.
One extra round.
Yes, who wants to play an extra round?
No, wait.
I was with Waner yesterday.
You want to play extra?
No, I won with him.
Don't we have a privilege?
Can we choose our partners first?
You choose.
No problem.
Sure.
Choose.
I
I choose Young.
Which one do you want to play?
Come on, choose your segment.
Then we'll choose one.
I choose three.
Then I'll also play fruit.
I also wanted to play the fruit one.
We win and then
we can eat the fruit, right?
Sure, no problem.
I don't know why he chose me.
Very unexpected, yes.
Yes, quite unexpected.
I think this time I have the initiative.
Then I definitely want to choose someone
I want to get to know.
So I chose Young.
Then Waner chooses
I'll choose CH then.
OK?
Which one do you want to play?
Which one do you want?
We'll play, you choose.
I can't play the fourth one.
Because I think my hand.
Your hand won't be able to, right?
Yes.
Then can we play the first one?
OK.
OK, play the first one.
We'll play balloon popping.
Come on, Alan, you choose.
I choose.
I'll choose you.
Which one do you want?
Which ones are left?
Two and four are left.
Do you want the cookie or...
Cookie.
OK.
Then who plays four for the second time?
Me, I'll choose you.
OK, sure.
So Elio will handle two segments.
Come on, everyone get in position.
Should we practice first?
Let's do a practice run.
OK, sure.
Come on, we
I'll go to two first.
Then I'll.
Everyone to their positions.
I'll wait for you at the last one.
When you play, I'll be at the last one.
Come on.
Let's give it a try.
Alan.
It's my frst time.
Wait, not enough.
Not enough.
I think that one is the hardest.
Which?
The third one.
I think this one is okay.
First stuff it all.
Yes.
I think ours is the easiest.
We think it's the easiest.
No need to rehearse.
Yes.
I think theirs is pretty hard to do.
And then like this.
This is so hard.
Yours is really hard.
What do we do?
Do you have a method?
Your privilege chose the hardest one.
I thought it was like this.
Just like this.
Like this and then just drop it.
It's pressed against the forehead,
and then the forehead has to keep
rolling down to the bottom.
Let me try, let's try.
Do we have a method?
Just transport it.
Then from the eyes,
face,
then to the neck,
then down.
OK, down.
Keep going.
Almost.
No, I suggest you
roll it from the forehead this way.
Otherwise it'll definitely
fall off at the chin.
Maybe choose
a smaller fruit.
Can hold it with your mouth then.
OK.
Just move down.
OK, smaller one with mouth works.
But just roll it.
How did it become biting?
They said use the forehead.
No, it starts from the forehead.
It has to start from the forehead.
So hard.
I know.
I'll just bite it directly.
I think that last one
was almost successful.
Don't make it so hard on yourself.
He can really hold it with his mouth.
What does that mean?
What?
Just wiping it with the fruit.
Can we really do this?
Is this really okay?
It really is possible.
It really went from the forehead down.
Never mind, I'll roll.
You'll roll? OK.
I'll roll it.
Switch to an orange.
This orange is all sandy.
Don't use this one.
I already bit it.
Come on.
I want to sit too.
What do you mean?
I need to use this.
Yes.
Yes, press closer.
Then.
Yes.
It falls.
Wait, don't drop it.
Let go.
OK.
Good, yes.
Almost.
OK.
Almost there.
So.
We don't need to practice ours, right?
Ours is very simple, right?
Yeah, we just hold each other.
Just roll while holding each other.
No need to practice.
Everyone, the time for all four segments
combined cannot exceed 1.5 minutes.
Come on.
Wait.
Go.
Need three.
Three? I thought one.
This doesn't count, right?
Take another one.
This is the easiest.
This is very simple.
So your privilege chose the hardest one.
I didn't know.
OK.
OH MY GOD.
You really didn't kiss?
This is already very small.
Actually our lips did touch.
Because the requirement is 1cm.
1cm is really too close.
Yes, if you need to
maintain a certain distance,
then definitely
it's less than 1cm.
I feel a little
embarrassed.
A little shy.
They've already succeeded.
They've already succeeded, hurry up.
(LOST IN THE DRAMA, TASK FORGOTTEN)
What are you doing?
Us two.
Come on.
Almost successful.
Down.
No, I'm not.
Success.
Stand up, success.
OK.
OK, we succeeded.
Quick, roll.
OK.
This is definitely 1.5 minutes.
1.5 minutes must be enough, right?
Enough, right? Should be 1.5 minutes.
How long?
Didn't pass?
Fruit violation.
Where was the violation?
Only one person can move.
So after I squat down, I can't
I can only stand.
OK.
Come on.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Oh no.
Quick, adjust the position.
This.
Adjust.
Oh no.
Wait.
Restart.
Oh, OK, OK.
It's fine, again.
This balloon.
Why is this balloon still so hot?
Crooked.
Come on.
Push hard.
It's hard for me to put into words
how I felt at that moment.
Because at that moment, I felt many things.
I wanted them to win quickly,
and I also wanted...
I don't know anymore.
I feel like someone is
paying attention to me,
and I think it's Tyler who
would pay attention to me.
He was sitting on that mat,
and
facing directly toward our mat.
Because I was also paying attention to him.
Wait.
Did they add
something into it?
Why is the balloon still so hot?
Ready, go.
Not started yet.
I'm ready.
OK, go.
What's going on?
Didn't pass.
So.
Joel didn't measure the distance.
Didn't you measure the distance?
OK, I admit I measured
and we really didn't pass.
OK, restart.
Let's do it again.
I hate you.
Come on, OK?
Let's do it again.
Ready?
We're ready anytime.
OK.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
Help him.
Oh my.
Oh my god.
Hurry.
Wait.
We both at the same time.
Those two.
Has it already started?
So fast.
Measure the distance, hurry.
Passed.
Our turn.
It's fine, only 40 seconds left.
There's still time.
Steady.
No rush, I'm watching.
Come on.
I'll move forward, it's fine.
Don't be afraid.
Wait.
I can... I can't move, right?
Yes, you can't move.
So it's rolled to
where has it rolled?
It's rolled to my neck.
OK, it's down.
Down again.
OK, it can still roll.
And now we two
still have space.
Steady.
Pressed together.
Squat little by little.
I can't squat.
He squatted, that's a loss.
Oh no.
Dropped.
One more time.
There's still time.
No, continue.
Wait.
Don't be afraid.
Get closer.
Wait.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-five.
It's really not here that
things go wrong, it's there.
Twenty-seven.
Almost winning.
Twenty-nine.
Time's up.
You can move it a bit below the forehead.
It's fine.
It's okay.
One more time, it's fine.
It's probably because I
because of my problem,
I caused this game to fail.
And we restarted.
I felt a bit like a child
afraid of being scolded.
Although I usually seem
very carefree
and don't
care about anything,
but inside my heart,
I'm quite sensitive.
Then I would feel very guilty.
But he didn't blame
me, he was very patient.
He was willing to step up
and help me get this done.
Ready?
Everyone OK?
Everyone's ready, OK.
Then let's start.
Three.
Two.
One.
Go.
OK, put it in the middle.
Just go slow, it's fine.
OK, come on.
Steady.
This round will definitely pass.
OK?
OK, come on.
It's fine, steady.
Should be enough, right?
Enough?
Enough.
Our turn.
Watching, I also leaned in.
Careful.
It's at the neck.
OK.
It's at the waist.
Elio, good.
Elio is so tired.
Stop the timer.
Time enough?
1 minute 35?
I'm done.
1 minute 35.
Even slower.
OK, let's do it again.
It's fine, let's go again.
Again.
I thought I.
It's fine.
One more time.
It's okay.
We just need to make sure
to crush it, pop it.
Come on.
Go.
Put it in the middle.
Don't put it to the side.
OK.
This balloon is so small.
It's so hard.
(NERVOUS WHIMPERS)
So nervous, choose one first.
Choose the smallest one, right?
One more.
Enough?
Passed.
Passed, hurry.
Only 30 seconds, we can make it.
OK.
It's fine.
Still 40 seconds.
Plenty of time, don't be nervous.
It's fine, take it
slow, there's still time.
OK, slow down.
Adjust.
Put it on the collarbone.
OK.
Caught it on the collarbone.
Hurry.
Wait, my legs are not...
Oh no.
Yes.
OK.
How many seconds?
We won.
Passed, right?
(ON CLOUD NINE)
Come on.
Let's go back first.
Get two trophies and get rid of them.
No, I don't want to see it anymore.
I'll refuse.
Then the lemon, how do
we deal with the lemon?
Who wants to eat the lemon?
We're back.
First, we need to choose
one person to be the pending person.
(Beach volleyball rules explanation)
And we have seven people, right?
Six left, and then
these six split into two teams.
A team of four and a team of three.
(Beach volleyball game rules)
Each team designates a protector
and a protectee.
The two must maintain
physical contact at all times.
The protectors of both
teams take turns using a ball
to attack the other team's protectee.
If the protectee is hit,
they are immediately eliminated.
That team must designate
one person from the remaining
to become the new protectee.
And maintain contact.
Until a team, due to elimination,
has only one person left,
that team loses.
The winning team
each member gets one surprise voucher.
(BLACK OR WHITE: TEAMING UP...)
Rock-paper-scissors.
Like this.
Probably most of the time,
it's impossible that only
one person is different.
Eliminate the palms-up ones first, then
majority follows minority.
The minority person comes out.
Then those in the minority
those few choose one more.
OK, good.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Come on, you two.
You two choose one.
Rock-paper-scissors.
But Alan today isn't.
Isn't today Alan's first
day? (HAND IN HAND)
Then today I'll let Alan
first pick the teammates
he wants, okay?
OK, I choose
I choose you first.
Pick them out first, okay?
OK, I choose
I choose you first.
Then choose.
Young.
OK, the three of us.
So the three of us are one team.
It felt like they
talked to me the most.
I prioritized choosing them.
Yes, and also that.
Start fighting over me.
Did you notice
you've become a two-person team?
He's not.
This one is definitely for me.
Sure.
People really are complicated.
When both teams were fighting over me,
I hoped that team could
successfully take me.
As the opposing side,
I also hoped
to be able to stay.
You can start.
Let's scheme on our own.
So we should go after
the protectee...
(STRATEGIZING...)
So actually the protectee can't move,
the other three can.
Let's think about that person first.
Only one person.
Go two by two.
Two by two.
Yes.
He just needs to hold onto me.
No, carrying me on your back is heavy.
Try it and see how to carry.
Carrying.
Carrying won't work.
I can't carry you.
Carrying is really...
No.
Maybe you.
No, I think you could just
have a part of your body
like pressing against him like this.
Just pressing against him like this?
Is this okay?
Hands like this.
Or just hold his arm.
And attack with one hand.
OK?
OK.
Come on.
Very complicated.
I just felt...
I don't know how to describe
how I felt.
I just felt
I just felt bad.
But I can't explain it.
So hard, bro.
Everyone's holding hands.
Don't keep wandering around the front area.
With only one hand, it's hard to operate.
Hit him.
They didn't hit.
Just started.
Yes.
Wait.
Get into position.
Come on.
We're the ones catching.
Come.
Can't get past, can't hit at all.
Stop faking.
It's actually really hard to hit.
Can't hit at all.
Eliminated just like that?
Yes.
It's just that Waner let
go of his hand himself.
I really don't know
why
I let go.
It's like he suddenly fell.
I tripped while dodging.
OK, send your next one.
Come on.
It's still him.
The loser has to serve.
The initial resistance
was very obvious.
I'll do it.
And then while playing,
I'm willing
and not willing.
But I can't explain it.
My true feelings are...
I don't really want to play with him.
Continue.
Hurry.
Wait.
I mean, when I hold him,
there's still a bit
of shyness.
I can actually feel that he
is a little shy.
Because he doesn't dare
to hold me tight.
Doesn't dare to have
moves that are too intimate.
And me holding him
can also reassure him.
Wait.
I won't leave anyway.
This is okay, right?
No, I'm afraid you'll let go.
When he took the initiative to grab my arm,
only then did I want to
hold tighter.
Look at the camera.
But I didn't let go.
Doesn't count, right?
Yes, doesn't count.
I didn't let go.
Then we continue.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Come on.
Nice move, zero damage.
But it's really hard to hit you.
Yeah, because I keep dodging.
Scare him.
Don't go out of bounds.
We won't.
Call him, hurry.
This is so hard.
Wait, I'll take off my glove,
my lucky finger glove, toss it.
It's full of sand.
I saw him throw that thing away.
I also know that if his hand
is cut like that,
catching that ball would
hurt a lot.
But I don't want to...
I don't want to care.
I can only choose to escape and ignore.
I don't want to actively
send any signals anymore.
Come on.
You.
Wait.
Come on.
Hook fingers, hook fingers.
I think if the range were a bit bigger,
it might be a bit better.
Because you moved the line.
Our feet aren't out of bounds.
But I feel the line moved outward.
I'm serious.
We two barely moved.
I feel like we barely moved.
Yeah.
It's actually quite hard
to hit you from the front.
He blocks so tightly.
Yes.
OK?
I feel my arm
is so uncomfortable.
Playing from dawn till dusk.
(CAUGHT OFF GUARD)
(MISSION FAILED)
Almost.
Close.
You wish.
He reacts too fast.
Scheme exposed.
You wish.
Scheming again.
He's doing this again.
Don't move.
There's still some distance
from the line, it's fine.
So tired.
The more we played, everyone
we two felt we were playing more and more
openly.
There wasn't that
barrier anymore.
Who's on?
That big swing was a fake, right?
Yeah.
Instant.
This feeling.
All I can think of is an "instant"
in my mind,
fleeting.
A thought,
and immediately maybe
suppressed by my own rationality.
When he hugged me, it was like
he wanted
to hold me tight,
but also
afraid it might be too much.
The hug was
not that tight.
And then
later on,
the hug got quite tight.
Just wouldn't let go.
And when I pulled him, it was like that.
I should have caught it.
Should have caught it and thrown it here.
Yes, I should have caught it and thrown it.
Thrown it out.
Hit.
So smart.
I started.
They're so smart.
I feel like,
I feel a chill on my thigh.
Good job, bro.
I think our coordination
is actually quite high.
We even scored.
And that
I remember that round was deadlocked
for a very long time.
I thought we couldn't hold on.
Come on.
Come on, I'll watch you two.
OK.
Are you tired?
Want to switch?
That works too.
I'll do it.
I'll be the protector.
Hold onto me tight.
Almost.
Just take advantage and
only attack in the gaps.
My turn, right?
Teammate, I'm coming.
I saw the line was crossed.
Saw the line crossed.
He let go.
Does letting go count as a loss?
We won.
These two rounds ended in 3 minutes.
Indeed, this one has strength.
It's different.
Strength makes a difference.
Come on, let's hug.
Come on.
OK.
Thanks.
You've worked so hard.
You go first, bro.
I'll do it.
A little tired.
What's this? Let's see.
A new one again.
Mission, mission is here.
Looks like we can order, everyone.
It's a menu.
Come take a look.
Specialty ingredient set.
So many.
Vouchers.
We won these this afternoon, right?
Yes, how many?
Two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten,
eleven.
So that round was seven.
That's seven.
Yes, and we have four from the game now.
So.
We can exchange.
First, third, fourth.
Exactly eleven.
Fruit, dessert, and specialty ingredients.
OK, then we choose
one, two, four.
Fruit, dessert, and specialty ingredients.
Thanks.
So.
I
What? Go ahead.
(FLUSTERED & BLUSHING)
I
You say it.
I want to drink that.
Which one?
Drink set.
Because I think alcohol is
something that amplifies emotions.
So it can also help people
quickly close the distance.
I think if everyone drinks a little,
they can open up a bit more.
I think drink set must be ordered for him.
Yes, I think so.
We want drink set and
special ingredients set.
Could we get the fruit for free?
May we?
May we, teacher?
Teacher, say something.
Please.
Thanks.
So lavish.
Help yourselves.
Let's start.
This bottle is one glass.
No.
This bottle should be two glasses.
I also want some coconut water.
That
yours.
Sir, what would you like to drink?
Can I get a bottle of coconut water?
No problem.
Little rice cake.
Done.
So blue.
Did everyone pour drinks?
Everyone did.
Let's have a toast then.
Cheers.
OK.
Cheers, welcome.
Alan.
Welcome, Alan.
Nice work.
Celebrating our hard-earned feast.
So great.
Today we can all chat.
Shouldn't we say it now?
No, because we've actually been holding it
for three days without talking about this.
Age?
Yes.
I knew it.
OK, still the first to rule out
someone who just graduated.
No, because today
I told Waner privately,
I said,
today we're out,
I said we have thirty,
almost thirty, I'm thirty.
And Waner said,
Who's thirty? Is there a thirty?
What's going on?
I said I don't know.
Then how do you know?
No one can tell.
Yeah, that's exactly it.
That's why it's shocking, who's thirty?
Who?
But.
No, this is a guessing game.
What's going on?
How old are you?
Me?
Guess.
What year do you think is thirty?
1996.
You're the same age as my sister.
Are you '96?
Are you older than '96?
You're not '96.
Earlier or later?
You're older than '96.
Guess.
1989.
1993？
'89?
What do you mean, bro?
I think it's '93.
How do you know?
I guessed.
I'm 32.
What's the zodiac for '93?
'93 is Rooster.
But I think
he totally doesn't look like it.
Because his mentality
completely doesn't show it.
Thank you, bro.
I want to ask,
who would actually think
he could be ten years older than me?
Who would actually think
you can't tell at all?
Are you '03?
I'm not even 22 yet.
Are you '03 or '04?
Bye.
Goodbye, bro.
'04.
My birthday is September 27th.
OK.
Waner, how old are you?
I'm '01.
OK, bye.
So young.
How old are you?
What do you think?
You're also pretty much post-2000.
Yes, I'm post-2000.
Post-2000.
OK, bye, I'm leaving.
'02.
I'm leaving.
I'm leaving right away.
Neither.
'03.
No, I'm the youngest here.
'05.
I'm '04.
He's even younger than you.
I'm November.
I'm two months younger than him.
You.
Ah, I just look older.
Are you '04?
No, you don't look older.
Don't look old.
I know, I just look older.
I look more mature.
OK.
Really can't.
Me? I'm '04.
Goodbye, I really...
Why is it so,
everyone is post-2000.
One '04.
Because you haven't asked me yet.
Wait, so on this side
automatically split into post-2000s,
and this side split into '90s.
You're a '90s kid.
Yes.
How old are you?
What '90s year are you?
Guess.
'98.
We're about the same age.
No.
Then aren't you '03 or '04?
Our ages
are about the same.
'99.
We're about the same age.
Our ages are similar.
'96.
Really?
'94, '95?
He's '98.
'98.
That's still young.
Because '98 is only
28.
OK, what's up?
Your turn.
'98.
I am '99.
OK, actually I'm not '04.
How old are you?
Actually I am ’94.
Maybe go down and run a bit first.
Then you must be a '90s kid.
You're in our age range.
Right?
99 or 98?
(Next Episode)
How about we play some drinking games?
Sure.
Then let's play Truth or Dare.
So which of us six
do you feel the most...
The one that makes
you feel like you and him
might have some
things you don't get along with.
"Project XY"